[Jesse Frederick singing
"Everywhere You Look"]
♪ Ahh ahh ahh ♪
♪ Ahh ♪
♪ What ever happened
to predictability ♪
♪ The milk man the paper boy
evening TV ♪
♪ How did I get to livin' here ♪
♪ Somebody tell me please ♪
♪ This old world's
confusing me ♪
♪ Clouds as mean
as you've ever seen ♪
♪ Ain't a bird that
knows your tune ♪
♪ Then a little voice
inside you whispers ♪
♪ Kid don't sell your
dreams so soon ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ Everywhere you go ♪
♪ There's a heart ♪
♪ A hand to hold onto ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ Everywhere you go ♪
♪ There's a place ♪
♪ Of somebody who needs you ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ When you're lost out there
and you're all alone ♪
♪ A light is waiting
to carry you home ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ Ahh ah ah ah ♪
♪ Chip-a-dee-ba-ba-bow ♪♪
♪ I pledge my love
and loyalty ♪
♪ To all the hive
and every bee ♪
♪ Our motto is
and ever was ♪
♪ buzz buzz buzz ♪♪
Please be seated.
Girls, as you know,
in my youth, I was a honeybee.
Now, I'm not the kind of person
who likes to brag
but my hive voted me queen bee
and retired my antennas.
Sounds like bragging to me.
Okay, all you honeybees
it's time right now
to welcome into the hive
a new honey of a bee.
Let's hear it for
Michelle Tanner.
[buzzing]
Please save all your
buzzing until the end.
Okay, it is time
right now
for me to present
to you, Michelle.
The official honeybee sash.
You know, honey,
I-I can't believe
you're my last little baby bee.
You know, I've put
three bees through the hive.
I don't mean to drone on
but who better to drone with
than a bunch of bees, huh?
Daddy, my sash.
Oh, right, sorry.
Excuse your antennae.
There you go.
How come I don't have
any badges?
Because you have to earn
them by doing projects.
You know, I had so many badges,
I had to wear two sashes.
In fact, I earned a badge
for earning the most badges.
Somebody's bragging again.
♪ Oh Lumberjack Jess
and Ranger Joe ♪
♪ Friends forever
wherever they go ♪
♪ Through thick in thin
they'll never part ♪
♪ One has hair
the other has heart ♪♪
- What do you think?
- You're fired.
What? Fire..
Oh, huh, I get it.
You want your name first.
You're such a baby.
- Ranger Joe.
- Uh, Jess, Jess.
Forget about the music.
- You're still fired.
- What?
There's been some big budget
cuts down at the station
and they decided you're out.
I almost said to 'em,
"Hey, if he goes, I go."
But I really like it there.
You're really firing me?
I'm fired?
Why? Fire him.
Get rid of the woodchuck.
Look, I'll do the dumb jokes,
I'll wear the stupid outfit.
I'll do anything
but sit on your hand.
Jess, look, I don't know
how to break it to you
but, uh, we don't pay
him a salary.
He's a puppet.
What am I doing?
I'm begging to be
on a kiddie show.
I'm jealous of
a buck tooth beaver.
Nah, this-this wasn't my dream,
to be on a kiddie show. I..
You know what?
This is a sign.
I'm gonna put all my energy
right back into my music.
You know what? I just heard of
this new label, Fat Fish Music.
I'm gonna put a great
demo together
and get it to them right away.
You know what, Joseph? Thanks.
You actually did me a favor.
Yeah, my pleasure.
If I'd known
you'd be so happy
I would have fired
you weeks ago.
Oh, Comet. Perro Muy bien.
Boy, Deej, you sure are going
to a lot of mucho trouble.
Well, I have to get my dad
in the mood.
I can't just say,
dad, I'm going to Spain.
He worries when I say,
dad, I'm going to the mailbox.
My parents were really excited
when I told them about Spain.
They already bought me
a one-way ticket.
Okay, everybody,
you can come down now.
Hola, me familia.
She said, "hello, my family."
Whoa-ho, que pasa.
He said, "Whoa-ho,
what's happenin'?"
[speaking in Spanish]
She either said,
"dinner's ready"
or "it's time to
clip your nose hairs."
Okay, Deej, what do you want,
how much is it gonna cost me
and why is the dog
wearing a hat?
Well, there's this summer-study
program in Barcelona.
No.
I'll get to live with
a Spanish family.
No.
I'll get to study the language
and expand my horizons.
- No.
- Doesn't that sound exciting?
No.
So you're not saying that I'm
not allowed to not go, right?
What did you just say?
I don't know, I just wanted
to get you off that no thing.
Uh, Danny, come on.
At least think about it.
I mean this is D.J.'s chance
to learn about a new culture.
Yeah, come on, Danny,
remember that one summer
when we took that
trip together?
Joey, we rode our
bikes to Oakland.
Dad, when D.J.'s in Spain,
can I have her room?
Oh, that's very caring.
Deej, this is a big decision.
I need some time to think
about it, honey.
Dad, please, this is a once
in a lifetime opportunity.
Don't worry, Mr. T,
I'll be with her every minute
as we sample the art,
the music, the tango.
[tango music]
Come on, Mr. T,
we wanna see the world.
Alright, Kimmy, let's start
with the back door.
Adios.
Ole.
Look, why don't we just
sit down for dinner.
I'm serving paella.
- Oh, muy bueno.
- 'Oh, muy bueno. Gracias.'
Who's ready for dessert?
Michelle's trying to
earn her first
honeybee badge for cooking.
You gotta taste it.
Well, I guess it wouldn't hurt
to have dessert as an appetizer.
I call it Michelle's
pudding surprise.
Oh, sounds delicious.
What's the surprise?
I think it's cheese.
Surprise.
Michelle, you put
cheese in the pudding?
Velveeta and that's not all.
Hmm, olives.
Don't you like it?
No, it's-it's very
different, honey.
- Good.
- Mm-hmm.
Then how come
nobody's swallowing?
- Hey, everybody.
- Hey.
- Hi, honey.
- Oh, fiesta. Cool.
How did it go with
the record company?
Yeah, so far, so good, I mean
at least they heard of me.
They're gonna listen
to my tape and get back to me.
Let me tell you guys something.
I have a feeling something
good's gonna happen.
Whoa.
But that's not it.
That was awful.
Michelle cooked it.
I was trying to get
my honeybee badge.
Oh, I didn't say awful.
No, no, no, I said awfully good.
Boy, that's awf..
You know what?
In fact, I'm gonna
have some more.
Here we go, see there?
Hmm-mm.
Velveeta?
And, uh, olives, is it?
You could stop eating.
I know you don't like it.
Ah, you know, Michelle,
you know what?
We'll give it to, uh..
We'll give it to Comet.
Hey, Comet will like it,
he likes anything.
Here you go, Comet.
I guess it needed more olives.
Are you laughing?
- Look at that. What's that?
- Feel that.
- See that bunny's tail?
- See that?
What's that?
Oh, can you feel that?
It's soft, huh?
It's soft like your big jelly
belly. Give me that thing.
Uh-uh. The hair, the hair.
Let go of the hair.
I know you're jealous.
Hey, give me that,
give me, give me, give me that.
Becky, what color
is that hair?
It's, uh, gray.
What?
Well, it's a l-light shade
of black
resembling the color gray.
I have gray hair?
Well, just a couple of 'em.
What?
Here, here, here you go.
Stay right there.
How can I have gray hair?
I'm only 29,
I can't have gray hair..
Yank 'em. Yank 'em.
Yank 'em.
Okay, but they say for every
gray hair you pluck
two more grow in its place.
Drop that hair.
Jess, would you relax?
So you have a couple
of gray hairs.
At least you still
have your hair.
Yeah, but for how long?
I feel it receding. I'm..
You know what,
I'm feeling it in my sleep.
I-I know how to check for this.
I know how to check.
Oh, my God. It's moved
four millimeters north.
Beck, I'm gonna have one
of those foreheads
that starts at my eyebrows
and go all the way
to the back of my neck.
[telephone rings]
There, see? The word's out.
It's probably
the hair club for men.
Talk to me.
Oh, sure I'll hold.
It's David Janolari
from Fat Fish Music.
Yes, Mr. Janolari, hello.
Oh. Aha.
Oh.
Thanks for crushing
my dreams so fast.
Alright. That's okay, bye.
Oh, honey, I'm sorry.
He said they like my music
they like the sound,
they like the look.
They just don't hear
a hit single.
Jess, look, I know
it's disappointing
but you can't let it
get you down.
You know what?
I have an idea.
How about tomorrow, you and me,
the boys spend the day together?
Come to the studio, okay?
The Beach Boys are
gonna be on the show.
Come on. They're your friends.
Like I wanna be around
The Beach Boys.
They had hit records
when they were 18.
I'm almost 30,
I got nothing.
Jess, life is not a contest.
Honey, things happen
when they're supposed to.
I don't know.
Well, time's runnin' out.
So is my hair.
This is so frustrating.
I mean, what happens if
I never make it
in the music business?
Dad, come on.
The suspense is killing me.
Can I go to Spain
with Kimmy or not?
I know when you're
tryin' to make a decision
that could change
the entire course of my life
the last thing
you wanna be is pushed.
So you won't catch me
pushing you.
No, siree.
No pushin' here.
- Deej.
- I know, I'm pushing.
I'm backing off.
Sweetheart, I told you,
I just, I gotta think
about this a little more, okay?
Deej, have you seen
your Uncle Jesse?
- He's upstairs.
- Oh, great.
Jess, come on down!
(Jesse)
'I'm kinda busy.'
Jess, this is really important.
Come on down now.
Deej, your uncle Jesse
is gonna flip.
Mike and Bruce from
The Beach Boys are here.
[screams]
I promised them some good
old-fashioned home cooking.
Quick, call chicken on wheels.
Come on in, you guys.
- Hi.
- Oh, hi.
Hey, when do we eat?
Thirty minutes or less.
Ha, she's a kidder.
Jess!
What Becky?
What's so important?
Whoa-a, The Beach Boys.
Whoa-a, Miss Clairol.
- Hi. Dr. Love, how you doing?
- How you doing?
- Bruce.
- How you doing, man?
It's the beach boys
and I got my..
Well, thanks for the warning.
Well, how did I know you'd
be dyeing your hair.
Why are you dyeing your hair?
'Cause I'm worth it.
Well, honey,
Mike and Bruce came over
because they heard you had
a new studio
and-and they'd like to jam.
- Cool.
- And eat Becky's home cooking.
Becky can cook?
I mean, boy, hey,
when she cooks, look out.
Hey, that's cool you guys
wanna play, that's great.
I'll call the guys,
they'll be over in ten minutes.
You know, it'd be good too
because It'll give me time
to comb out
and rinse, otherwise..
...I'll streak.
♪ If every word I said
could make you laugh ♪
♪ I'd talk forever ♪
♪ I ask the sky
just what we had ♪
♪ Mmm it shone forever ♪
♪ Oh-ho ♪
♪ Forever forever ♪
♪ I've been so happy
lovin' you ♪♪
Ha ha!
[applauding]
You guys, that was
totally excellent.
Totally.
Let's eat.
That is such a cool song.
I sang that song to Becky
at our wedding.
I'll tell you, you know,
if I had a song like "Forever"
I'll bet you, Fat Fish Records
would sign us like that.
You want it, you got it.
Leon, please pass the coleslaw.
You mean it?
We can record "Forever"?
Sure, as long as Becky keeps
cookin' up food like this.
Well, I'll give you the phone
number. I mean, recipe.
Well, I mean this is cool.
That'd be..
That would great
if we did, I mean..
You know, normally we record
you know, stuff that we write.
But quite frankly,
who's buyin' it?
But you know what, Elvis never
recorded anything he wrote.
I wonder what it'd been like
if Elvis had done
a Beach Boys' song.
♪ If everybody had an ocean ♪
♪ Across the USA ♪♪
That's scary.
[laughing]
How about it
like this, though?
♪ If everybody had an ocean ♪
♪ Across the USA ♪
♪ Then everybody'd be surfin' ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Like Californi-a ♪
♪ You'd seem 'em wearing
their baggies ♪
♪ Huarachi sandals too ♪
♪ A bushy bushy blonde hairdo ♪
♪ Surfin' USA ♪♪
[all applauding]
Hey, munchkin,
give me a good-luck kiss.
I got this
great version of "Forever"
that I cut with The Beach Boys.
I'm taking it down
to Fat Fish Records.
I'm telling you somethin',
they gonna love this baby.
Will you taste
my new recipe?
Oh, that sounds tempting.
Alright, you know what,
I'll take just
a really tiny little sample.
Just give me a little tiny
sample, okay? Here we go.
Mm-hmm.
Interesting. What is it?
Tuna cream.
So that would be tuna and..
Oreo ice cream.
I'll never get my
cooking badge.
Oh, now, come on, I don't wanna
hear that kind of talk.
I mean, you know,
tuna cream may not be
one of the 31 flavors.
But you gotta have perseverance.
Persa what?
Perseverance, it means, y-you
know, you-you never give up.
You keep on trying.
Look at your Uncle J.
I've been-I've been
plugging away
at this music business
for 10 years.
I've been writing songs,
taking goofy gigs, you know why?
Because I will do anything
to keep my dream alive.
♪ We're caught in a trap ♪
♪ I can't walk out ♪
♪ Because I love you
too much baby ♪
♪ I said buy me those
Kitty Krispies man ♪
♪ And I'll be your best friend ♪
♪ Me-owa Me-owa ♪
♪ Oh hey there Mr. Egghead
you scientific dude ♪
♪ Whenever you're around
I'm in a scientific mood ♪
♪ You can tell us
how the bird flies ♪
♪ Or how the fungus grows ♪
♪ The creation
of the universe ♪
♪ Or how we blow our nose ♪
♪ The farmer in the dell
the farmer in the dell ♪
♪ Viva la stereo
♪ The cheese stands alone
the cheese stands alone ♪
♪ Honka honka stinky cheese
♪ When you're laughin' ♪
♪ Or when you're chucklin' ♪
♪ Oh the sun it is comin'
shinin' through ♪♪
One, two, three! Down.
[laughing]
♪ Glow little glow-worm
glimmer glimmer ♪
♪ I gotta gal that I love so ♪
♪ Glow little glow-worm glow ♪♪
- You see what I mean, Michelle?
- You were desperate.
Yeah, I never gave up. You know
why? Because I got, what?
Perseverance.
Right on, munchkin. Yeah.
Alright, let me give you
a little tip, now, alright.
You like pudding,
you like cheese
so you put them together.
You like ice cream and tuna,
again, you put them together.
Stop putting things together.
You gotta lose the combo deal.
Just try one thing.
Try something simple.
Thanks, Uncle Jesse.
I love you.
I know.
- I love you too.
- I know.
What was I thinkin'?
It needs olives.
Would you please tell me
if I can go to Spain?
Okay, look, I've been
thinking about Spain.
You gotta understand,
this is a big decision.
It's a decision that I've been
wrestling with all day.
And if you know anything about
wrestling, which I do
because I was dorm champ
in the 145-pound class
You know, I was really
wiry back then too.
They used to call me
the human pipe cleaner.
Forget it, Deej,
you're not goin'.
Not necessarily, sometimes
when he rambles, it's good news.
How would you know?
He never gets to the news.
Kimmy, don't be rude.
He might change his mind.
We don't know what
he's gonna say.
Maybe we want him to
change his mind.
Maybe he hasn't
made up his mind.
Maybe you want me
to lose my mind.
Dad, I can't take it anymore.
Just tell me either way.
Okay.
You promise you'll
write me every day?
Of course, I'll bring
stationery, pencil..
I'm going? You're letting
me go? Thank you.
Good decision, Mr. T. She
already told the school yes.
Well, I said,
"yes, unless my dad says no".
Okay, follow me.
OJ's on a stick.
Get them while they're cold.
- Oh, thank you, sweetie.
- Oh, look at that.
Okay, boys, are you ready
to taste your first popsicle?
Oh, that's good, huh?
Happy tongue.
Fruity, sophisticated
yet mischievous, huh-huh.
And best of all,
it comes on a stick.
You mean it?
You really like 'em?
- Yeah, these are very good.
- Right.
Well, guess what?
The incredibly talented chef
who made OJ's on a stick
is our very own
Michelle Elizabeth Tanner.
I did it! I can cook!
Congratulations, honey,
you're gonna get
your first honeybee badge.
Thank you.
I may open a restaurant.
Hey, everybody,
this is, uh, David Janolari
from Fat Fish Music.
- How are you doing?
- Hi.
Hey, a real family. Cool.
This guy has the best ear
in the music business.
That's strange, yesterday,
you said he wouldn't know
good music if it bit him
on the--
[laughs]
Kids, don't you love 'em?
Listen, you guys aren't
gonna believe this,
that-that's why I brought David
over because if he says it
you have to believe it,
tell 'em.
Well, I heard the kid's tape of
"Forever" and it blew me away.
I'm not even here.
I had no choice,
I had to sign him.
- Honey, he signed.
- Congratulations.
I'm finally gonna have
a record out.
Ten years of struggling
has finally paid off.
'Cause you
got perseverance.
Cool kid.
Hey, Jess, cat, let's rap.
When you think of major
superstars
like Michael Jackson
or Hammer
what do you see?
Funny pants?
No, no, no.
You see dancing.
- I do?
- Of course you do.
That is why we are gonna take
that sweet little song of yours
re-record it, turn up
the energy, pump up the beat
and make the hottest dance
video ever to hit MTV.
Uh, Dave, cat, uh,
there's just one small problem.
I don't dance.
Oh, come on, a guy with your
looks and talent, can't dance?
- I don't believe it.
- Believe it.
- Yeah, that's right.
- My dog, comet's better dancer.
Anyway, don't worry about it.
'Cause when we get
through with you
everyone in this country
will be dancing
"The Jess Man."
The Jess Man?
[instrumental music]
Listen, uh, Dave,
I-I'm not
not really a rapper.
Vanilla ice said
the same thing.
Yeah, come on.
Give it little bit more.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Now, give me that kick.
Give me that kick.
- I got the kick.
- Yeah, yeah.
[instrumental music]
♪ Ahh ahh ahh ahh ♪
♪ Chip-a-dee-ba-ba-dow ♪♪
[theme music]